{
    "id": "94d2e52ea9ae47958622f5f71a1c1030",
    "title": "Across, Over, Above, Through",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I saw him climbing ………………… the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0f69f87578149ddb18e601c752d09ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "See if you can jump ………………….. the stream.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0075b9d6f9d44e688d1f34640d235aaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "We swam ………………….. the river.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47da195169334bf39304e7d73f78ec9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked ………………….. the ice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8964b62cd6e4d2cbf428934fa035abe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane was flying …………………… England.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "480a746b8c1548bab34809a5a7980405"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a little cottage ……………….. the lake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e106a96ede14b40bde6190a33d6bd74"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you see the helicopter hovering …………………. the palace.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a1ef8175d9b44cc944c3e5d18202ce2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked ………………… .. the wood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c38c90a92f3a49ffa3a2c4e4b826a937"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was wearing a coat …………………… his pyjamas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d9c806d10be945b48d8b139603cce80b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your daughter is well ………………… average in intelligence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4124e3b133949cdbfdaf07c0384c78f"
        }
    ]
}